One way in, no way out
Tower of Evil is a horror film directed by Jim O'Connolly.
A group of experienced archeologists are searching for an old and mystic Phoenician
treasure when they are surprised by a series of mysterious murders...
Evan Brent, played by Bryant Haliday.
Rose Mason, played by Jill Haworth.
Nora Winthrop, played by Anna Palk.
Superintendent Hawk, played by William Lucas.
Dr. Simpson, played by Anthony Valentine.
Brom, played by Gary Hamilton.
Tower of Evil (also known by the titles Horror on Snape Island and Beyond the Fog) is a 1972 British horror
film directed and written by Jim O'Connolly and starring Bryant Haliday and Jill Haworth.
The film explores themes of treasure, exotic island, fog, proto-slasher.
The tone is dark.